eventure.com 2013-09-08

# Commitment to Privacy

PRIVACY COMMITMENT

Website Privacy Statement

Last Updated: January 1, 2013

Scope and Changes

Live Event Media, Inc. (OTC: LEVT), dba eventure ("LEVT" or "us") operates the website,  [www.eventure.com](http://www.eventure.com/) and permutations thereof that refer to this Website Privacy Statement in a direct hyperlink (the "Website").

LEVT respects your privacy and we want you to be confident in sharing your information with us. This Website Privacy Statement is designed to inform you of the types of information we collect from users, how we use that information, and the circumstances under which we will share it with third parties. This Privacy Statement applies only to the Websites. It does not apply to your use of any other websites (whether or not operated by us), including any websites which we provide links to or websites of our partners or advertisers, or to any activities which are not online.

Please note that some features and/or services referenced may not be available on some Websites. Therefore, portions of this Privacy Statement which pertain to such features or services may not be applicable on each of the Websites.

This Website Privacy Statement is effective as of the date listed above. Even if you read and/or agreed to a prior policy statement, you need to review this updated version. We reserve the right to revise this Website Privacy Statement at any time and at our discretion. If we decide to change our Website Privacy Statement, we will post those changes to this Website Privacy Statement accessible on the homepage of the Websites, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via either email or by posting a notice on the Websites for 30 days.

A Special Note About Children

We do not knowingly market to or encourage children, minors or anyone under the age of 13 to use our service and we request that children do not submit information to us.

Personal Information and How We Use It

LEVT operates a social network offering users a set of tools to connect to our global community.  Generally it is possible to use the Websites without providing us with any personally identifiable information, but on some of our Websites, users have the option of providing various types of personal information to make the best use of available services and features. This section describes what we collect and how we use it. Providing the information is always voluntary, however, and you can always choose not to provide the information by choosing not to use the service or feature. By providing the information you agree to our use consistent with this statement.

INFORMATION SUBMITTED BY YOU

Zip Code Only: On some of the Websites, you have the choice of providing your ZIP Code. We use your ZIP Code to compute your location for simple profile matching and product shipping and sales tax estimates. In connection with some of the matching services we provide we may also use your ZIP Code to match you with third parties offering services in your area.

E-mail Address Only: On some of the Websites if you wish to sign up as a registered user, register for either Price Alerts (through our Watch List feature) or our Buyer's Alert Newsletter, provide reviews, be matched with participating service providers, we require that you provide us with your email address. We will use this to email you with the Price Alert, the Buyer's Alert Newsletter, and other information or service provider match results you may have requested.

Basic Contact Info: On some of the Websites a user may be able to become a registered user. When a user decides to become a registered user, we ask for some basic contact information, such as username, ZIP Codes, and email address. We use this basic contact information to facilitate the use of certain features of our Websites and to send you information about our company, services and products, and to communicate occasional offers from our partners and advertisers if you elect to receive them.

Complete Profile Info: In our online registration form, we ask users provide us with certain information such as name, email address, gender, date of birth, location details and some optional details. These details are available to the user at anytime, and capable of being corrected or updated (with the exception of gender and profile address) through the users "Profile" page.

At the users own discretion, he/she may choose to post additional facts about themselves. These facts may include sensitive personal data such as ethnic origin, level of education, religious denomination, sexual life and physical or mental health. Users may volunteer sensitive personal data to us when they create their profile. Please also remember that photographs and videos that are posted may reveal sensitive personal data about e.g. about one's health. If the user volunteers sensitive personal data to us, they explicitly consent to our using such information as described in this Privacy Policy.

On some of the Websites a registered user may decide to become a seller. When registering as a seller, we collect complete contact information, i.e., full name, address, e-mail address, and phone number, as well as credit card number and expiration date. We use this information to validate the seller's identity and to bill the merchant for services provided by LEVT and approved in advance by the seller. All credit card information is encrypted.

Service User Information: On the Websites where it is available, if a user wants to receive potential personal "match" information, LEVT requests that users of certain Website services complete a questionnaire, which includes personal and contact information ("Service User Information"). Service User Information enables LEVT to provide Service Users with information specifically about requested services.

Content Submitted By You: When a user chooses to post content on any of the Websites where posting is available, for example, in the form of a photo review we may collect and maintain that information in a file specific to the user.

Correspondence Submitted By You: When a user sends us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about activities or postings on the website, we may collect such information into a file which is only accessed by authorized personnel. We may also collect other users' comments about a user in our complaints department.

INFORMATION ACQUIRED AUTOMATICALLY

We collect certain information on the Websites through the user's experience and activities, cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that detail their viewing preferences, activities and interactions with LEVT. Consequently, collected information is tied to the user's personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to the Websites, and, subject to the Opt-Out Policy stated below, to direct pertinent marketing promotions and communications to them.

Cookies: A cookie is a piece of data tied to information about the user and stored on the user's computer. We use both session cookies, which terminate when a user closes his browser, and persistent cookies, which remain on the user's computer until manually deleted. Cookies are used to help make your use of our Websites more enjoyable. LEVT creates these cookie files on your hard drive through your browser and uses them to save information on your LEVT username, ZIP Codes and Website preferences so you can avoid re-entry of this information each time you visit our Websites. Cookies also help us to deliver content specific to your interests. You may decline our cookies if your web browser software permits, although this may prevent you from accessing certain features on our Websites. For more information about deleting and controlling cookies please visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)</a>

Log Files: Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the Web site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We use your IP address at times to help identify you as you browse and to gather broad technical and demographic information on who uses our Websites. We do not tie log files to personally identifiable information.

Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs): We employ and/or our third party advertisers employ a software technology called clear gifs (also known as Web Beacons or Web Bugs). They help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content and which campaigns are effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics, about the size of a period at the end of a sentence, with a unique identifier. Clear gifs are similar in function to cookies and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In addition, LEVT and its advertisers may use clear gifs in HTML-based emails. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns by showing how many emails recipients have opened. We do not tie web-beacons to personally identifiable information.

GENERAL USES OF INFORMATION

In addition to the uses described above, we may use your personal information for any of the following:

To contact you in response to a customer service question from you, or in relation to any issue arising in respect of the agreement between LEVT and you, or to resolve or attempt to resolve a dispute between users or between LEVT and you

To process credit card payments approved in advance by you

To allow you to send an email to another user who is on the LEVT site, where available

To assist law enforcement or other governmental agencies investigating cases of possible illegal activities by third parties

To improve the experience of using the Websites, improve LEVT's products and services, improve marketing and promotion of our products and services, customize the Websites' content and layout, and generally improve the Websites to meet your needs better

To make your profile data available to other users of the website if you select the 'Any users' access setting.

Who We Share Your Personal Information With

Aggregated information: We aggregate personal information into statistics about users, their usage of the Websites, traffic patterns, and demographics. We may provide third parties with such statistics, but never in a way that would make the information personally identifiable: this data is aggregated from millions of users to the Websites each month.

Advertisers: If you choose to submit to us your Complete Contact Info as part of a request to be contacted by an advertiser or advertisers, we will supply to the advertiser(s) your Complete Contact Info and those advertiser(s) will contact you using the information regarding the specific query which you have raised. Advertiser(s) that receive your Complete Contact Info may contact you regarding other products and/or services. If you choose to submit to us a questionnaire which includes Service User Information, we may provide the information submitted in that questionnaire to any of our participating advertiser(s) who may provide the products or services to which your request relates. Your submission of the questionnaire will be your consent to our disclosure to any such advertiser(s). LEVT does not have control over the use of the Service User Information once provided to sellers(s): your rights in respect of their treatment of your information will be governed by their own policies.

Processing Agents: We may from time to time use external service providers to facilitate or outsource elements of our service or operation of the Websites, including without limitation the use of agencies to process credit card transactions.

Business Transfer: As we continue to develop our business we might buy or sell companies, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing privacy policy. In the event that our company, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired, your information may be one of the transferred assets and we may share it with an actual or potential acquirer.

Legal Requests and Customers' Requests: We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries and third parties to enforce all applicable laws including but not limited to laws relating to intellectual property rights, fraud, and other rights. Therefore, we can (and you authorize us to) release your name, city, state, telephone number, email address, previous fraud complaints, if any, and other account and personal information without a subpoena, court order or other substantially similar legal procedure to law enforcement entities when we believe release is necessary to comply with the law to protect the rights, property, or integrity of the Websites, our customers, users or third parties, or to prevent illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threat to the physical safety of any person, or violation of LEVT's Terms of Use. Further we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email, and company name to consumers who have alleged fraud or any other consumer dispute relating to their transactions and/or communications with you.

Other Trusted Parties: We may provide your contact information and other personal data to trusted third parties to provide information on products and services that may be of interest to you.

Accessing and Changing your Personal Information

For registered users on the LEVT Website, a user can review personal identifiable information by logging in with the user email and password and then clicking on the "Profile" link located at the top of each page. After accessing the user's Account, click the appropriate link under the Profile section to make changes as necessary. Users will be able to review and change much of their personal information, including but not limited to:

Contact email address;

Profile, photographs, and videos;

City, region, and country of residence;

Password.

For access and changes of any other data, please [contact us](mailto:contact.us@eventure.com). Upon receipt of your request, and possibly subject to identification measures, we will provide you with reasonable access and comply with appropriate data correction requests in accordance with applicable law. For access requests, we will respond within thirty (30) days upon receiving your request.

You should also note that if we have provided your information to third parties, you will have to make a separate request to them directly if you want to have your information removed from, or corrected in, their databases.

Control of your password: You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If, despite the foregoing, you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. This can be done via your "Profile" page.

Security: LEVT has security measures in place to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. LEVT uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information such as firewalls. While "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, our technical team at LEVT works hard to ensure secure use of our site.

Deleting Your Profile

Users of the LEVT network have the following choices to delete their profile from our database:

Send a message to Customer Service; and

Sign in with your password and delete your profile

These options are available from your "Profile" page

Invite a Friend

If a user decides to use LEVT's Invitation option to invite a friend to our site, we ask them for the friend's email address. LEVT will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to join the website. LEVT stores this email address for the purpose of automatically associating the friend with the user sending the invitation. LEVT does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations. The friend may contact LEVT to request the removal of this information from our database.

By providing us with information about a friend, you confirm that they have given you their informed consent to do so.

Uploading your Contacts

If a user decides to upload their contacts, they accept that by doing so, an email invitation will be sent on their behalf, to the email addresses of the contacts that have been uploaded and then selected to be invited. LEVT stores the name and email address of the contacts for the purpose of automatically associating the friend with the user sending the invitation. LEVT does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations.

Your Use of Other User's Information

You may not use other users' information for commercial purposes, to spam, to harass, or to make unlawful threats. We reserve the right to terminate the accounts of those who misuse other users' information or who otherwise violate the Terms of Use.

Third Party Advertising and Links to Third Party Websites

Third parties displaying advertisements on our Websites may also use cookies or clear gifs which are activated when you click on those advertisements. LEVT does not control the use of cookies and clear gifs by third parties. The use of cookies and clear gifs by these companies is subject to their own privacy policies, which you may review by visiting their websites.

Choice/Opt-out Policy

We understand you may not want to receive email from us or from our partners and advertisers. You can choose to opt-out of receiving email communications from us - and from our sharing your contact data with our partners and with advertisers for direct marketing purposes - by selecting to opt out if and when you register on our Websites, by following the unsubscribe instructions in the email communication or by contacting the partner or advertiser directly.

To opt out of receiving all other LEVT mailings after you have registered click the appropriate unsubscribe link contained within the email that you receive. Please note that opting out may prevent you from receiving email from LEVT regarding updates and improvements to the Websites or offers and promotions we may be offering.

In some cases we request that you submit personal information in order to forward this information to our partners that have products or services in which you may be interested. In the event we share this information with our partners, we no longer have control over the use of such information and your rights regarding such use will be governed by the policies of our partners. You will then have to contact them directly with any opt-out request.

Inactivity

If you have not signed in to the website for 6 months, we may remove your profile as part of our data cleansing process.

Your California Privacy Rights

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits residents of California who are registered users and use our service for private, family or household purposes to request certain standard information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes (including a list of categories of data disclosed in the previous calendar year and names and addresses of data recipients). To make such a request, please contact us as provided below.

Internet Crime Complaint Center

LEVT wants your Internet surfing experience to be safe. Help protect yourself. If you believe you have been a victim of Internet crime you can file a complaint with the Internet Crime Complaint Center (IC3), a partnership between the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) and the National White Collar Crime Center. Their website is <http://www.ic3.gov/>.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Website(s), or your use of the Website(s), please contact us at

Live Event Media, Inc.

3420 Bristol Street, 6th Floor Costa Mesa, CA 92626
